Andrey Arutyunov

Full Stack Developer

Petah Tiqwa, Israel+972-53-228-73-41

in linkedin.com/in/andrey-arutyunov

Summary

Ambitious software developer with 4 years of experience in SaaS development (both back and front end), looking for a full-time full stack developer position. Curious of learning new skills, motivated for constant progress

Languages and technologies: C# (.NET): MVC, WCF, Web API; HTML/CSS/JavaScript; Angular JS/Angular 10; TypeScript; NgRx/Rx.JS; Angular Material; Docker; Unity IoC, Node.js; Java (basic knowledge); Git; TFS; SQL Server; Redis; GraphQL; PostgreSQL; Mongo DB (basic knowledge)

Work experience

Senior Full Stack Developer

05.2021 - Present

bolttech, Israel

- Created and maintained new company projects within multi tenant insurance exchange environment (e. g. new consumer flow insurance interview HQX 2.0 for Progressive one of the biggest insurance agencies in US, modern quick quote consumer interview platform for insurance agencies in Italy)
- Worked on Angular web projects using modern technologies (NgRx/Rx.js, Angular 10) as well as backend apps (REST APIs, .NET microservices (Owin WebAPI), Redis consumers)
- Worked on device/browser compatibility issues implementing the UI tasks according to design kits (Figma, Adobe XD)
- Involved in constant production support, investigated and solved environment related issues and delivered hot fixes
- Advised team members on features development/troubleshooting for new company projects (multi tenant insurance exchange environment), making code reviews, lead trainings for new employees, made a major contribution to internal Wiki knowledge base)

Full Stack Developer 01.2019 - 05.2021

bolttech, Israel

- Maintenance/Development of insurance agency web platform for US clients (.NET MVC, WCF, AngularJS/Angular 5), implemented complex app features (e. g. collaboration with Bind HQ™ insurance platform, AMS (US agency management system) transaction management assistant)
- Built new services/APIs by using microservices architecture (SOA) in multi-tenant (multi configuration) environment
- Took a major role in upgrading and refactoring several legacy projects (e.g. security improvements for old MVC projects, Angular JS major upgrades, migration of legacy monolith projects to a new platform (BoltX) for several clients)
- Worked in Agile environment, participated in features design, involved in all Scrum meetings

Backend Developer 12.2017 - 01.2019

SaleFreaks, Israel

- Worked on company core projects (e. g. billing service, admin dashboard, back office) using modern .NET technologies
- Implementation of integrations with foreign APIs (e. g. Intercom, PipeDrive, eBay/Amazon API)
- Constant work with databases (PostgreSQL): building complex queries for preparing reports and database management
- Maintenance of existing projects (troubleshooting, developing fixes)

Technical Support Lead 09.2017 - 12.2017

SaleFreaks, Israel

- Worked on SaleFreaks platform leading software solution for sales process automation in e-commerce: provided service to company customers, handled technical problems with accounts, cooperated with development team on solving the issues
- Worked with bug list (bug description and revision, provided possible solutions), to-do lists (using Slack, Trello), , prioritizing tasks and features, team work, servers management

Education

Software Development

04.2016 - 10.2017

Tel Ran College, Israel

- Backend development (Java, Spring, Hibernate, REST), frontend development (HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery, AngularJS, Angular 2+, Bootstrap), experience in working with databases: SQL, MongoDB and operation systems (Windows, Linux)
- Participated in final project 'IsraEzer' (development of Angular 2 website and administrator dashboard, support in server development)

Computational Linguistics M. A.

2013 - 2015

Southern Federal University, Russia

- Studied the methods of human identification by language parameters using dedicated computer software: voice recognition and analysis using computer software tools (spectrogram, vowels searching etc.);
- -Foreign languages learning (German, English) in all aspects (Phonetics, Grammar. Literature etc.)